

SARAWIN BUAKAEW

Address: 18/1 M.3, Bangsmak, Bangpakong, Chachoengsao

Phone: 061-503-6105

Email: sarawinbuakaewpp@gmail.com Website: https://sarawinb-engi.github.io

SUMMARY

Instrumentation Systems Engineer currently working as an Electrical Engineer with experience in Facility Maintenance, Solar Rooftop, BESS, BAS, and PLCs. Passionate about integrating electrical engineering with software development to create efficient solutions. Currently developing skills in Python, AI, Web Development, iOS App Development, and Generative AI to enhance system analysis and automation capabilities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrical Engineer, Amita Technology (Thailand)

Nov 2023 - Present

- Developed and optimized electrical maintenance strategies, improving system reliability and reducing unexpected failures.
- Enhanced energy management in facility operations, leading to improved efficiency and cost savings.
- Compiled and analyzed power consumption data, providing detailed reports to identify energysaving opportunities and improve efficiency.

BangPakong Power Plant (Intern)

May-July 2022

- Creating a report on topic Turbine Supervisory Instrumentation System
- Creating a report on topic CEMs (Continuous Emission Monitoring System)
- Experice Calibration Instrumentation equipments (Pressure gauge, Transmitter and Other).

BangPakong Power Plant (Intern for MOU)

Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

- Learn about operation of the power plants (Thermal Plant, Gas Turbine and Generator)
- Practicing calibration of measuring instruments such as pressure gauge, proximity vibration etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Instrumentation & Electronics Engineering, 2.93 GPA

May 2021 - June 2023

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok

- Major in Instrumentation System Engineer.
- Thesis on "PLC and Industrial Robotic arm control with Robot Operating System (ROS)".

Diploma in Power Electricain, 3.70 GPA

May 2018 - May 2020

Chulabhorns Technical Colleng (Lat Kwang)

- · Major in Electrician
- Thesis on "Smart Home V.1"

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- **Technical Skills:** System Integration, PLC, Electrical Power, Python programing Robotics, BAS Controls, Instrumentation Calibration
- Computer Skills: Word, Excel, Pivot, Power point, Visio, PowerBl
- · Languages: Thai, English.